Alright in this clip we are going to be going over how to go over the bags that we are stacking up.
These are great to do and it is going to help you to get higher and start jumping a lot better for your double leg.
If you touch it, you don't want to touch it because if you do they are going to fall over.
These are very wobbly and it is going to really push you to not touch and get over and they are also very soft so you won't get hurt.
All these are punching bags and if you practice martial arts they should have them or if you are doing gymnastics in a place they should also have other things that you can stack up that are very soft that you can practice going over.
Alright so same motion and you should be able to do your double leg by now going over the mat and that is the best way to practice getting it down so now let's go ahead and practice going over these.
O'kay you can see as I went into my double leg, same motion, same thing but this time I really tried to clear it without touching it so this is great practice if you want to practice going over people for performances it looks great, o'kay.
Another good thing these are good for is when you start doing your double things at a certain height it is a mind thing, when you start taking the stuff away it gets harder to do your double legs so as you get it and you get more comfortable with it start taking them off.
So actually start high and then start going lower and lower just like that and then soon you will want to get all the way to the ground without anything.
You are going to find this is the most challenging spot because in your mind you are not going to push yourself to jump as high and some people as soon as they take this away they just go this low and bam fall to the ground.
That is why these are really good practice to use for the double legs.